# Sevda Amini-Uhde

# Junior Web Developer





sevda@sevinu.com

www

www.sevinu.com



**in** Sevda Amini - Uhde





#### **CAREER INTERESTS**

Internship Entry level positions including:

- Junior Web Developer
- Junior Front-End Developer
- Junior Full-Stack
  Developer

### ABOUT

I have recently finished a Diploma of Information Technology through an intensive Bootcamp at Coder Academy in Brisbane. I have worked in academia as a researcher, in Environmental Consultancy and Customer Service over the past 10 years, however, I have developed a passion for computers since the first time I connected to internet through a Dial Up modem. You can see more about my soft skills, programming languages I speak and the tech-stack I use in my <a href="GitHub">GitHub</a>, <a href="LinkedIn">LinkedIn</a> and <a href="may website">my website</a>.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Freelance Projects**

- <u>Shandell On Trend</u> (A WordPress website developed for a fashion/styling business)
- <u>Bardon Hair Design</u> (A WordPress website developed for a hair and beauty business)
- Eyelash Business (A full-stack React website to provide services and sell products. In Progress and In Documentation Stage)
- <u>Robin Blue Portfolio</u> (A full-stack portfolio website developed by Ruby on Rails for an artist)

# **Personal Projects**

- Portfolio (V2) (HTML, SaaS, JavaScript)
- Portfolio (V1) (HTML and CSS)
- <u>Wedding Invitation</u> (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

# Other Projects (Developed at Coder Academy)

- She Rydes (A MERN e-commerce website for women motorcycle apparel- In Progress)
- Just Like Granny (A full-stack Ruby on Rails two-sided marketplace application - The Second Version Is in Progress)
- Little Recipe App (A terminal app developed with Ruby)
- Space (JavaScript Hackathon Project)
- Rotten Pumpkins (Express Hackathon Project)

#### EXPERTISE





























#### **MY TOOLS**

- Visual Studio Code
- Sublime
- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Git
- cPanel
- Postman
- Slack
- Agile Project Management

#### REFERENCES

The contact details of the references will be provided upon request.

## **EDUCATION**

Diploma Information Technology (IT) Coder Academy | Brisbane | Mar 2020 - Jan 2021

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) **Environmental Science** Griffith University | Brisbane | Mar 2011 - Mar 2015

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Counter Manager David Jones | Chermside | Aug 2019 - Mar 2020

**Environmental Scientist** Environmental Earth Sciences (EES) | Brisbane | 2016-2018

Researcher Griffith University | Brisbane | 2011-2015

#### AWARDS

- Diversity Scholarship Container Camp AU 2019, Sydney 25-26th July 2019
- International Postgraduate Research Scholarship (Tuition Fees) **Griffith University** March 2011- March 2015
- Postgraduate Research Scholarship (living allowance) **Griffith University** March 2011- March 2015

#### **VOLUNTEER WORK**

- University of Queensland (UQ) Aug 2018 Assisted in developing a critical environmental compliance obligation register as part of the Enterprise Compliance Management Framework for The University of Queensland.
- Queensland University of Technology Mar 2018 Assisted in completing Health, Safety and Environment projects.

#### INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

- **Painting**
- Reading (Classic Novels, Autobiographies and Science Fiction)
- Watching movies (Detective, Comedy and Fiction)
- Making Puzzles